jobinrwanda.com 2019-07-17

# Job in Rwanda Privacy Policy | Job in Rwanda

Job in Rwanda collects personal information and distributes that information to help in connecting employers with job seekers with similar interests and to provide other services. This policy describes how information is collected and distributed and your choices with respect to your personal information.

**Information We Collect and Retain**

We collect the personal and demographic information you choose to provide us. We also collect information about how you use our sites and the areas of our site that you visit. We may also acquire information about you from third parties in order to further personalize your experience. The resulting logs contain information necessary for analyzing the use of resources, troubleshooting problems, and improving services. We also use cookies.

**How Information is Used**

Information you post in public areas of the site or placed in the searchable Resume database will be accessed by employers operating in Rwanda or abroad. We strive to provide a safe, secure environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users, but cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized users store or transfer information downloaded from the database, so you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information to Job in Rwanda.

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, and to operate and improve our sites. Our services include the display of personalized content and advertising on our site or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We may use your information to contact you about Job in Rwanda site updates, conduct surveys, or informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

**Disclosure of Information to Others**

We share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of our own products and services to you. These third parties may not use that information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services.

If you have consented for us to do so, we may use your information to contact you about other products or services available from our affiliates.

If you have consented for us to do so, we may also share your information with third parties who may contact you about their products or services.

We can also share information where legally required. Information collected on our Sites is stored in whole or in part in Rwanda, and may be subject to Rwandan law.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may review, correct, or delete the personal information you submit to us at any time. If your personal information was previously accessed by others using the Sites, we are unable to delete the information from their systems.

Job in Rwanda has no control over the information that other third parties may have about you. We encourage you to visit their web sites and review and read the privacy policies and opt-out practices that govern their usage.

You may also turn off cookies in your browser but this may affect your use of the site.
